ilgamos.com 2015-03-15

# ILGAMOS

**Privacy Policy**

**Introduction**  
[www.letsgetgold.com](https://www.letsgetgold.com/www.letsgetgold.com) (the site) and its owner respects the privacy of all partners, visitors and users (you) and is committed to protect it.

Our Privacy Policy guidelines regulate  
• how the site handles data provided by or collected from you,  
• how those data are collected,  
• what types of personal data are collected,  
• how those data are used, shared and protected,  
• how long data are kept,  
• what your rights are and how you can contact Ilgamos with issues relating to personal data collected and stored by the site.

How your personal data may be collected or obtained by Ilgamos.com

Your personal data may be collected or obtained in the event of any of the following taking place:  
• online registration through the site  
• making contact via email or phone  
• completing forms (eg. newsletter subscriptions, etc.)

When you log into the site, we may use "cookies" or other similar tools designed to collect certain  
specific information about the use of the site when you enter, view or browse through the site.  
"Cookies" are small data files files that are placed on computers and other devices used for surfing  
the internet and browsing throug web pages. "Cookies" may be used for various purposes, for  
example to get information about visitors' browsing habits or to analyse web page usage. You may  
elect not to accept "cookies" by clicking on "Settings" and "Privacy Settings" in your browser. Please  
be advised, however, that your browser my not perform certain functions adequately if you block  
"cookies". These "cookies" are not aimed at collecting personal information about you.

**Data collection, deleting personal data**

Ilgamos warns all members, users and visitors every time data is about to be collected. Personal data  
may only be collected after users and visitors have read the information about data collection and  
accepted the terms. Users and visitors may not be obliged to provide data, they provide data on a  
voluntary basis. However, Ilgamos wishes to point out that in the event members, users or visitors  
refuse to provide data, certain functions may not work properly and some user platforms may not be  
used by them.

You are entitled to request Ilgamos to delete all data collected from you and – at the same time – to  
cancel your registration, if a registration has already been made.

How Ilgamos may use personal data collected from users and visitors:

Your personal data will be used by Ilgamos to: -  
• respond to all comments and questions received from you;  
• process your online purchases and activities on the web page;  
• make improvements on the web page and make it more user friendly;  
• investigate occasional complaints from users and visitors about the web page.

What types of personal data may be collected by Ilgamos?

After registration, Ilgamos partners accept the Terms and Conditions and also commit themselves to  
upload the copy of a personal ID document and proof of residential address, under our KYC (Know  
Your Client) guidelines.

Partners are advised to upload only basic personal data which are absolutely necessary for Ilgamos to  
handle queries and comments and provide satisfactory answers to questions from partners.

Ilgamos will never collect any special data or information about its partners, such as data relating to  
partners’ race, ethnic background, political views, religious beliefs, sexual preferences, memberships  
in trade unions or parties and health condition. If you – contrary to prevailing international data  
collection rules and regulations – upload special information about yourself to Ilgamos’ database, the  
company will delete such information with immediate effect and your registration will be cancelled.

Ilgamos will never sell, rent or trade personal data collected from members, users and visitors.  
Ilgamos may only share personal data in the following events:

• Transferring personal data of one partner to another partner within the Ilgamos system,  
when it is necessary for standard business purposes;  
• Providing information to partners about products and services ordered from Ilgamos;  
• Sharing information with selected outside service providers, such as bank account and bank  
card providers (these providers are not allowed to use personal data collected for their own  
purposes);  
• Providing information to government agencies or other parties if it is reasonable to do in the  
interest of protecting the rights and property of Ilgamos or its partners and/or safeguarding  
its security.

**Protection and storage of personal data**

Ilgamos maintains the technical and human resources infrastructure necessary to guarantee the full  
protection against any accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, transfer or  
use of its clients’ personal data.

Ilgamos operates under a tight internal privacy policy to ensure no unauthorized person may ever  
gain access to your personal data. Under this policy, only authorized persons may view or handle  
client’s personal data.

**Duration period of storing personal data**

Ilgamos only stores personal data (given by clients at registration or occasionally on a voluntary basis  
thereafter) until such data is permanently deleted. In the event that you decide to delete personal  
data given at registration or any time thereafter, storage of your personal data discontinues and all  
personal data are removed from the system and safely destroyed.

**References to other web pages**

Occasionally, Ilgamos’ web site may contain link(s) of other web sites with a privacy policy that may  
differ from that of Ilgamos. Ilgamos takes no responsibility for the privacy policy and/or data  
management practices followed by these other third persons. It is recommended that before you  
begin to browse among other web sites or share any of your personal data or other information you  
familiarize yourself with the privacy policy and data management practices of those web sites.

**International data transfer**

Personal information collected from you may be transferred to the parent company of Ilgamos or  
any of its subsidiary companies in the future. These companies may not be registered and operating  
in the country of your residence where you provided your personal data. Other countries may have  
data protection laws and privacy protection standards that are different from the country where data  
was originally provided. Whenever your personal data may be transferred to another country,  
Ilgamos will ensure those data will be protected in exactly the same way as they are protected under  
our Privacy Policy within our system in the country of providing the data.

**Modifications of the Privacy Policy**

Ilgamos reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Our clients will immediately be  
notified of any change in our Privacy Policy via email communication. Any change in our Privacy  
Policy will become effective on the day they are published on our www.ilgamos.com web site. We  
recommend that you regularly monitor the text of this Privacy Policy in order remain up-to-date.

**Your rights and obligations under this Privacy Policy**  
• You may disclose your personal data and share them with other parties only at your own  
responsibility.  
• You may exercise your right to access, modify, delete or hide your personal information, and  
also to object to the use of any data processing procedure;  
• It is in your best interest to keep your personal data up to date at all times so please make  
sure you notify Ilgamos of any changes in your personal data and contact details.

**Contacting Ilgamos**

Should you have any questions about or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you wish to  
exercise any of your rights as outlined above, please don’t hesitate to contact lgamos on this email  
address: [support@ilgamos.com](mailto:support@ilgamos.com)
